<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
    <id>switchboardbridge</id>
    <name>CLARIN Switchboard bridge</name>
    <summary>The Switchboard bridge sends selected files to the CLARIN Language Resource Switchboard.</summary>
    <description><![CDATA[
**Directly send files from your personal cloud store to the CLARIN Language Resource Switchboard.**

This app extends the user interface of Nextcloud files app with an option to open the files in the Switchboard.
Once clicked, a new browser tab opens with the Switchboard website pre-loaded for the selected file. From
there, the user can discover a variety of language-related processing tools and call those tools with a single
click.



When selecting multiple files within Nextcloud, an option button is also made available in the files-batch
options section. This option will open a new tab with the Switchboard for each selected resource.

The files' settings section allows the configuration of a custom URL for the Switchboard. This is useful
since there are multiple running instances, e.g. https://beta-switchboard.clarin.eu where the newest tools
and feactures are available.

For more information about the CLARIN Language Resource Switchboard visit:
- **https://switchboard.clarin.eu** - main running instance of the Switchboard
- **https://github.com/clarin-eric/switchboard** - main repository for the Switchboard code
- **https://github.com/clarin-eric/switchboard-tool-registry** - metadata repository for all the tools available
in the Switchboard
- **https://github.com/clarin-eric/switchboard-doc** - various documentation, e.g. API specs, integration of tools,
integration in 3rd party applications (as is the case for this Nextcloud app)
      ]]>
    </description>
    <version>3.0.0-RC1</version>
    <licence>AGPL</licence>
    <author mail="switchboard@clarin.eu">CLARIN</author>
    <namespace>SwitchboardBridge</namespace>
    <category>integration</category>
    <website>https://switchboard.clarin.eu</website>    
    <bugs>https://github.com/clarin-eric/B2Drop2LRSwitchboard/issues</bugs>
    <repository	type="git">https://github.com/clarin-eric/B2Drop2LRS.git</repository>
    <screenshot>./img/screenshots/screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>./img/screenshots/screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>./img/screenshots/screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <dependencies>
        <nextcloud min-version="21" max-version="31" />
    </dependencies>
</info>
